https://mtygroup.com/privacy-policy/

Introduction
At MTY, we are committed to maintaining the highest standards of integrity in our business. In the course of business, it is necessary to collect, record, store, process, transmit, and otherwise handle Personal Information about individuals. We take these activities seriously and seek to provide fair, secure, and appropriate methods for the handling of Personal Information. All such activities are intended to be consistent with both generally accepted privacy ethics and standard business practices. If you have any questions or comments about MTY’s Privacy Policy, you can contact us.
Obtaining your consent
The purpose for which Personal Information is collected will be specified on or before the collection of the information, and any change of purpose will be communicated to you. This consent will be expressed in writing, given verbally, electronically, or through an authorized representative. In limited circumstances consent can also be implied.
Consent to collect, use, and disclose Personal Information can be withdrawn at any time, subject to legal and contractual restrictions and reasonable notice.
Limiting collection, use, disclosure, and retention of personal information:
Collection
Only required information for the purpose(s) identified will be collected.
Only lawful means will be used to collect personal information.
To the extent appropriate:
Personal Information will be obtained directly from you; and
Prior to collecting Personal Information from any other source, you will be notified or your written authorization will be obtained.
Use and disclosure
Personal information will not be used or disclosed for purposes other than those specified to you, except:
Where required by law; or
Where reasonably necessary, to determine eligibility for a benefit; or
To protect the interests of MTY against criminal activity, fraud, and material misrepresentation in connection with a contract.
Retention of records
Keeping Personal Information only as long as it is necessary, including for the purposes of updating the product or services or as required by law. When the Personal Information is no longer required, it will be destroyed either by shredding or other approved destruction methods to prevent unauthorized parties from gaining access to the information during and after the process.
Safeguarding information in our custody
We have developed and will maintain security procedures to safeguard Personal Information against loss, theft, copying, and unauthorized disclosure, use, or modification. Access to Personal Information is restricted to employees and authorized service providers who need it to perform their work. While MTY endeavors to protect all information, the most sensitive information, such as medical information, receives the highest level of protection.
Providing you access to your information
You have the right to be informed of the nature and source of Personal Information that MTY has on its records concerning you.
Should you wish to receive a copy of the documents MTY has on its records, minimal reproduction and handling fees may be asked. You will be informed of the charge before the documents are reproduced.
You also have the right to request the correction of inaccurate, incomplete, or obsolete information in your file. If demonstrated to our satisfaction that the information held in our record is inaccurate or incomplete, we will make the necessary changes.
Any request to access or correct information held in our records should be made in writing to:
info@mtygroup.com
If you are not satisfied as to how we have handled your personal information…
You may register a Privacy-related complaint by contacting:
info@mtygroup.com
We will explain our complaints handling procedure and inform you of other complaint procedures that may be available to you.
If a complaint is justified, we will take appropriate action to resolve the situation and if necessary change our Policies, Procedures, or Practices.
If you have any disputes with this policy, please contact MTY at info@mtygroup.com; or 8150 TransCanada Highway, St. Laurent, QC, Suite 200 H4S 1M5, and we’ll do our best to provide you with a prompt resolution.
About Us
Our DNA
Our History
Prizes and Recognition
Our Brands
Become a Franchisee
Our Expertise
Request Form & Process
USA Operations
Our website uses cookies to optimize your browsing experience and map website usability. If you agree to proceed using cookies, please click on ‘ACCEPT’. Otherwise, go to your browser settings to disable the functionality. Read MTY’s Privacy Policy to find out more.
ACCEPTPrivacy & Cookies Policy
Privacy Overview
This website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these cookies, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may have an effect on your browsing experience.
Privacy Overview
This website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these cookies, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may have an effect on your browsing experience.
Necessary
Always Enabled
Necessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.
Non-necessary
Non-necessary
Any cookies that may not be particularly necessary for the website to function and is used specifically to collect user personal data via analytics, ads, other embedded contents are termed as non-necessary cookies. It is mandatory to procure user consent prior to running these cookies on your website.
